SEBASTIAN CURTIS LAVARIAS WEB DEVELOPER

Mobile: 09972217704

E-mail: sebastiancurtislavarias@gmail.com

Web: https://bastilavarias.github.io Github: https://github.com/bastilavarias

Home Address:

406 Sta Fe St. Tondo Manila, Philippines

SUMMARY

I'm Sebastian Curtis Lavarias, 21 years old. I believe that great things can be done by a group of people through unity, trust, and teamwork. I make sure to follow through and finish the commitments that I have and I can adapt easily to different kinds of situations.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- HTML, CSS and JavaScript
- Vue.js / Sass
- PHP / Laravel / Node.js
- SQL
- Amazon Web Services
- Git

EDUCATION

Universidad De ManilaBS Information Technology
2018 - Present

Metropolitan Medical Center College of Arts Science & Technology

Senior Highschool 2016 - 2018

Tondo High School

Highschool 2012 - 2016

Magat Salamat Elementary School

Elementary 2006 - 2012

WORK EXPERIENCE

Web Developer

Malabon LGU (Outsourced) | Dec 2021 - Present

Web Developer

Fourello | Dec 2020 - Dec 2021

- Converted UI/UX designs to an interactive website.
- Developed responsive and mobile-friendly web applications.
- Implemented and made APIs according to the business requirements.
- Led a team consisting of developers to implement features to a project.